Finding Aid for the Alfred T. Hamilton Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Alfred T. Hamilton Papers
1858-1859
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0187
.03 linear_feet
Scope and Contents
This collection contains copies of letters written by Alfred T. Hamilton to his father, 1858 and 1859. He was a doctor in Franklin County, and his letters discuss the medical conditions of this patients as well as living conditions in the South. Copies of 2 letters from James B. Childs to Mrs. Noble in 1961 regarding the location of the town.
- Correspondence – Alfred to Father
  - May 23, 1858
  - June 17, 1858
  - June 24, 1858
  - July 7, 1858
  - July 10, 1858 – page 2 only
  - July 20, 1858
  - July 30, 1858
  - August 1, 1858
  - September 2, 1858
  - September 6, 1858
  - September 29, 1858
  - October 2, 1858
  - November 7, 1858
  - November 28, 1858
  - December 15, 1858
- Correspondence – Alfred to Father
  - January 5, 1859
  - January 25, 1859
  - February 1, 1859
  - February 9, 1859
  - March 1, 1859
  - March 10, 1859
  - March 17, 1859
  - March 19, 1859
  - March 20, 1859
- Correspondence – James Childs to Mrs. Noble
  - October 4, 1961
  - October 6, 1961